jewelscent.com 2014-06-29

# Privacy Policy | JewelScent

###  Privacy Policy

JewelScent ("Company," "we," "our," "us") knows that you care about how your personal information is used and shared. We take your privacy seriously and want to outline the measures we take in safe guarding your personal information. By visiting the jewelscent.com website and domain name, and any other linked pages, features, content, or application services offered from time to time by Company in connection therewith (collectively, the "Website"), or using any of our services, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy covers Company's treatment of personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") that Company gathers when you are accessing Company's Website and when you use Company services.

#### Your Profile Information

The information we gather from customers enables us to personalize and improve our services, and to allow our users to set up a user profile and make purchases via the Website. When you register (log in), you supply your email address and a password. This allows us to provide you access to your account every time you visit Company website. Before completing your first purchase, we also ask you for your name, phone number, email, billing and shipping addresses. This information, along with your credit card number, is necessary to fulfill your order. This information may be disclosed to specific members of our staff and to select third parties (such as our credit card processor and shipping provider) involved in the completion of your transaction and delivery of your order. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of many of our special features, and you may not be able to complete a purchase through the Company Website.

We may use your email address to notify you about the Company daily deals or to inform you of your order placement, order status and/or shipping information if you have opted-in. Emails are sent only to Company users who have chosen to receive them (opted-in) or who have made a purchase on our Website. At any time, you can notify us to opt-out from receiving these emails. In addition, we keep a record of your past purchases, returns, and credits. We may also ask you for information regarding your personal preferences and demographics to help us better meet better meet your needs.

Users of our Website are required to be at least 18 years old, and any user under 18 is not an authorized user. Additionally, if we learn that a user is under 13 years of age, we will promptly delete any Personal Information we have collected about that user.

#### Automatically Collected Information

Upon engaging Company website or services the Company automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, the type of browser being used, cookie information, the page you requested, duration of activity on our site and any items you may purchase. This information may be used to customize the content you see on our Website or to communicate with you about special offers. These statistics do not identify you personally, but provide us information regarding the type of user who is accessing our Website and certain browsing activities of that user. We may make extensive use of this data at an aggregated level in order to understand how our Company website is being used.

Please note that we have the ability to retain any data that you provide on our website(s), even if you do not complete your [registration/transaction] by clicking [submit/next]. Such contact details and data may be used to contact you to inquire why you did not complete your [registration or transaction. For more information, full details of our privacy policy can be found here [Policy](http://www.jewelscent.com/privacy)

#### Cookies

Like most other transactional Websites, we use "cookies" to improve your shopping experience and to save you time. Cookies are little tags that are placed onto your computer. We assign a cookie to your computer when you first visit us in order to enable us to recognize you each time you return. Cookies allows us to customize our website to your individual preferences in order to create a more personalized shopping experience. Please note that the cookies we use for our Website or email campaigns do not store personally identifiable information about you or your finances.  

#### Sharing of Personal Information

We neither rent nor sell your Personal Information to anyone. We share your Personal Information only in instances as described below.

We employ other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and need to share your information with them to provide products or services to you. Unless we tell you differently, Company's agents do not have any right to use Personal Information we share with them beyond what is necessary to assist us.

We restrict access to your Personal Information to those employees who need to know that information to provide products or services to you. At all times we take the utmost care to protect your personal information.

Company may be forced to disclose information in order to comply with a subpoena, court order, administrative or governmental order, or any other requirement of law, or when Company, in its sole discretion, deems it necessary in order to protect its rights or the rights of others, to prevent harm to persons or property, to fight fraud and credit risk, or to enforce or apply Company Website terms of use.

#### Secure Shopping For All JewelScent Customers

Your Company account Personal Information is protected by a password for your privacy and security. You need to prevent unauthorized access to your account and Personal Information by selecting and protecting your password appropriately and limiting access to your computer and browser by signing off after you have finished accessing your account.

When Company's order form asks users to enter Personal Information such as a credit card number, that information is encrypted with industry-standard Secure Socket Layers ("SSL") encryption to keep your online order safe and secure. Company also maintains physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect your Personal Information.

Company endeavors to protect user information to ensure that user account information is kept private.

This Privacy Policy only governs information collected on this website.

#### Changes In Policy

Company may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. You acknowledge that this Privacy Policy is part of the Terms of Use and you unconditionally agree that using this Website signifies your assent to Company Policy. Your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this policy and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages. If we make changes in the way we use Personal Information, we will notify you by posting an announcement on our Website or sending you an email. Users are bound by any changes to the Privacy Policy when he or she uses the Website after such changes have been first posted.  

#### Questions or Conerns

If you have any questions or concerns regarding privacy at Company site, please send us a detailed message to info@jewelscent.com and we will make every effort to resolve your concerns. You may also write to us at:

JewelScent Inc  
448 S. Hill St., Suite #712  
Los Angeles, Ca 90013

Effective Date: July 1, 2013
